Address: Horsens, Nørrebrogade 70, 1 th.

Mob.: +45 42 21 31 17

CV - Maksim Mirzinskij

Professional Profile

I am a young, software developer with marketing and project management background. I can do both, develop applications with the help of various IDE's and be part of a project management team.

Furthermore, I have a significant range of skills that can contribute an IT based businesses. Through my education and work experience, I worked out a habit to be curious in all sorts of IT advances.

I am quite passionate in developing my technical skills. Global Business Engineering education have allowed me to be part of numerous projects that I as an IT analyst had to provide solutions, both reflecting business and technical aspects

Finally, I am very motivated in career and experience growth. Have ambitions and not afraid of hard work. Honest in what I do and how I approach specific tasks.



Maksim Mirzinskij

Profile: Hardworking, social, honest, curious, motivated, ambitious.

Interests: Heathy lifestyle, friends, family, sports, music: guitar.

Contact

Birth: 22. November 1990

Profession: B.Eng. Global Business Engineering

LinkedIn: Maksim Mirzinskij

Education

2014 - 2019 B.Eng., Global Business Engineering, VIA University College

The degree qualifies me to fill managerial positions within design and implementation of technical solutions, as well as within marketing and sales.

During the program I have participated in several projects that dealt with finances, marketing and both web and software product developments. Bachelor thesis was based on UX implementation in software development.

1997 - 2009 High school, "Zaliakalnio" gymnasium

Address: Horsens, Nørrebrogade 70, 1 th.

Mob.: +45 42 21 31 17

Relevant Work Experience

2014 - 2018 Website developer at OpenUsource ApS

Have been working with website development using Drupal CMS. Mainly, participated in backend development. At the company, I have improved my programming skills and learned to work in a professional environment. Additionally, in such a small company communication played a significant role.

- Web Development
- Professional IT environment
- Communication Skills

2010 - 2016 Manual labor/team leader at Dansk Supermarked

I have worked in a warehouse where I was involved with logistics and manual labor. During my six years of hard work, I have managed to become a team leader. This work has helped me to improve my skills in becoming a goal-oriented manager and disciplined me in dealing with adversities.

- Management Skills
- Hard Work
- Ambition

IT skills

In terms of programming I have work experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript (Node.js, React, Redux), Java, SQL, C#, ASP.NET, WPF.

Capable of working with ERP system: SAP ABAP/4 Programming

Furthermore, accustomed with such IDE's: Android Studio, Visual Studio and Eclipse.

Have studied and worked with Oracle, Mongo and Neo4j databases.

Plus, I have a good understanding of Software Engineering techniques (Activity, ER, Use Case diagrams and etc.)

Daily user of the Office programs like Word, Excel, Project and PowerPoint.

Language skills

Can write and speak fluently Russian, English and Lithuanian. Currently learning Danish (beginner/intermediate level).

Address: Horsens, Nørrebrogade 70, 1 th.

Mob.: +45 42 21 31 17

Leisure

In my free time, I like being active and involved in various sport activities. For the last 3 years I have practiced Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu. With its help I became humbler and more disciplined.

What is more, I have participated in 5 km and 10 km DHL company runs. This experience gave me an understanding, how beneficial it can be for team-bonding. Hope, that at some point I can be part of Copenhagen's marathon run.

Finally, last year I have discovered diving and managed to become a certified diver. Underwater world fascinates me, I hope that I will continue exploring deep waters, in future.

In addition, in between my sport activities and studies I like to play guitar and read historic and scientific literature.

.